Contact

210-788-8547 (Mobile) michael.hillrn@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/michaelhill-mba-bsn-rn-cen-71a8b468 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Emergency Nursing
Certified Emergency Nurse
Critical Care

Certifications

Certified Emergency Nurse

Michael Hill MBA BSN RN CEN

Facility Administrator/Director of Nursing at Bluecloud Pediatric Surgery Center

Houston, Texas

Summary

Experienced nursing leader with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Emergency Nursing, BLS Instruction, Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS). Strong healthcare services professional with a Master of Business Administration (M.B.A.) focused in Health/Health Care Administration/Management from University of Texas at Tyler.

Experience

Blue Cloud Pediatric Surgery Centers 1 year 1 month

Facility Administrator/Director of Nursing January 2020 - Present (7 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Director Of Nursing
July 2019 - January 2020 (7 months)
Houston, Texas

Texas Children's Hospital Patient Care Manager August 2017 - July 2019 (2 years) Houston, Texas

North Cypress Medical Center
3 years 3 months

Clinical Nurse Manager

August 2015 - August 2017 (2 years 1 month)

Cypress, Texas

Registered Nurse
June 2014 - August 2015 (1 year 3 months)

Houston, Texas Area

EagleMed LLC Flight Nurse February 2014 - December 2014 (11 months)

American Traveler Staffing Professionals Travel Registered Nurse June 2012 - January 2014 (1 year 8 months) Everywhere

American Mobile Healthcare
Travel Registered Nurse
June 2012 - January 2014 (1 year 8 months)
Everywhere

CHRISTUS Health
Registered Nurse
January 2011 - May 2012 (1 year 5 months)
San Antonio, Texas Area

Education

University of Texas at Tyler

Master of Business Administration (M.B.A.), Health/Health Care

Administration/Management · (2015 - 2017)

University of the Incarnate Word

Bachelor of Science in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2006 - 2010)